U.S. Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations (Dunlop Commission) Documents 6220
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations (Dunlop Commission) Documents
1990-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations
6220
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
8258702
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Patrizia Sione, January 13, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
United States. Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations
8258702
- ILR Catherwood Library Hot Topic: "Future Worker" documents from 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bargaining for Pay Equity: A Strategy Manual, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: National Committee on Pay Equity
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- ILR Catherwood Library Hot Topic: "Future Worker" documents from March, 1991, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Poll on Striker Replacement and Other Labor Law Issues Released, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Employment Policy Foundation
    Notes: March 12, 1991.
- ILR Catherwood Library Hot Topic: "Future Worker" documents from December, 1992, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: An International Comparison of Investment Behavior as a Key to the Time Horizons of American Industry, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: Warren E. Farb; Andree C. Dumermuth
    Notes: December, 1992.
- ILR Catherwood Library Hot Topic: "Future Worker" documents from March, 1993, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Brown and Reich Announce Worker-Management Commission, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Mary Meagher
    Notes: March 24, 1993.
- ILR Catherwood Library Hot Topic: "Future Worker" documents from May, 1993, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: National Poll Shows What Public Wants From Labor Law Commission, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Bradley Cameron
    Notes: May 24, 1993.
  - Item 2: Minutes of Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations
- June 21, 1993 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Agenda for Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: June 21, 1993.
  - Item 2: Procedures for Presentations to the Commission, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Safer and Healthier American Workplaces Through Improving Knowledge, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: George L. Stelluto
  - Item 4: Influence of Technology on the Workplace and Worker-Management Relations, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: David C. Cranmer
  - Item 5: Competitiveness and Worker-Management Relations, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Waren E. Farb
  - Item 6: Outline of Statutes and Regulation Affecting the Work Place, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Labor Productivity, Compensation Costs, and U.S. International Competitiveness, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: United State Bureau of Labor Statistics; Office of Productivity and Technology
  - Item 8: Capabilities and Capital Investment: New Perspectives on Capital Budgeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Carliss Y. Baldwin; Kim B. Clark
  - Item 9: Minutes of Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations; Request for Comments, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Federal Register
    Notes: June 30, 1993.
- July 28, 1993 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Workplace Committee, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: July 6, 1993.
  - Item 2: Agenda for Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: July 28, 1993.
  - Item 3: Twelve Years of Workplace Cooperation: Ford and the UAW, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Peter J. Pestillo; Ernest Lofton
  - Item 4: Oregon OSHA: A Partnership Between Labor and Management, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Irvin H. Fletcher
  - Item 5: NORPAC Food Facts, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Lisa Trussell
  - Item 6: Joint Workplace Safety and Health Committees, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: John A. Pompei
  - Item 7: Memorandum of the Will-Burt Company, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Will-Burt Company
    Notes: July 19, 1993.
  - Item 8: VWC, Inc. Workplace Committees, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Cheryl Womack
  - Item 9: Breif on Labor Management Cooperation, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Michael Howe; Betty Bednarczyk
  - Item 10: The Impact of Quality Action Teams in the Workplace, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Federal Express
  - Item 11: Minutes of Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Schedule of Furture Meetings: September 1993 through April 1994, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- September 15, 1993 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Agenda for Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 15, 1993.
  - Item 2: Agenda for Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 15, 1993. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: A Summery of the Cooperative Partnership, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: National Steel Corporation
  - Item 4: Workplace of the Future, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Morton Bahr; William K. Ketchum
  - Item 5: Workplace of the Future, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Workplace of the Future, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 15, 1993. To be published in Human Resource Management Journal, v.32.
  - Item 7: Workplace of the Future, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 15, 1993. To be published in Human Resource Management Journal, v.32. Copy 2.
  - Item 8: Four Years of Jointness at Scott Paper Company and the United Paperworkers Intenational Union (UPIU), 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: John P. Nee; Donald L. Langham
  - Item 9: Toyota Motor Manufacting, U.S.A., Inc. Georgetown, Kentucky, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Robert J. Reid
  - Item 10: Toyota Motor Manufacting, U.S.A., Inc. Georgetown, Kentucky, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Commission on the Future of Worker/Management Relations, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Jerome M. Rosow
  - Item 12: Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations; Hearing, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 21, 1993.
- ILR Catherwood Library Hot Topic: "Future Worker" documents from October, 1993, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Debate Over Modifying the Ban on Employer Dominated Labor Organizations: What Is the Evidence?, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: James R. Rundle
    Notes: October 24-26, 1993. Prepared for the AFL-CIO/Cornell University Conference on Labor Law Reform.
  - Item 2: Reforming U.S. Labor Relations, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Joel Rogers
- November 8, 1993 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: News: Kathryn Turner Appointed to Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: June Robinson
    Notes: November 4, 1993.
  - Item 2: Agenda for Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: November 8, 1993.
  - Item 3: Statement of Lane Kirkland, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Lane Kirkland
  - Item 4: Exhibits to the Statement of Lane Kirkland, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Testimony of Jerry J. Jasinowski, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Jerry J. Jasinowski
  - Item 6: The Whirlpool Experience, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: William D. Marohn
  - Item 7: Whirlpool President Identifies Employee Empowerment as a Key to Success in Global Marketplace, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Robin R. Skiles
  - Item 8: Statement of the Labor Policy Association, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Bruce Carswell
- December 15, 1993 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Notice: Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations December 15, 1993,Public Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Office of the Secretary
    Notes: December 2, 1993.
  - Item 2: Agenda for Meeting, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: December 15, 1993.
  - Item 3: Burdens and Restrictions of Workplace Regulations on Small Business, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: William A. Stone
  - Item 4: Small Business and the Work Place, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Diane M. Orlowski
  - Item 5: Small Business and the Work Place, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Wendy Lechner
  - Item 6: Statement of Karen Nussbaum, Director, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Karen Nussbaum
  - Item 7: Statement of Karen Nussbaum, Director, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: December 15, 1993. Copy 2.
  - Item 8: Statement of Robert A. Georgine, President, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Robert A. Georgine
- January 19, 1994 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Dunlop Commission Report Acknowledges Importance of Employee Involvement Says NAM, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Monica Gliva
    Notes: News Alert, January 9, 1994.
  - Item 2: News: Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations to Meet January 19, 1994., Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: January 14, 1994.
  - Item 3: Agenda for Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: January 19, 1994.
  - Item 4: Statement of Daniel V. Yager, Assistant General Counsel, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Daniel V. Yager
  - Item 5: Statement of Howard V. Knicely, Executive Vice President, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Howard V. Knicely
  - Item 6: Testimony of Teamsters General Counsel Judith A. Scott, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Judith A. Scott
  - Item 7: Employee Owned Organizations vs. Employer Dominated Organizations, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Larry Cohen
  - Item 8: Statement of Richard A. Beaumont, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Richard A. Beaumont
  - Item 9: Testimony of Eileen Appelbaum, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Eileen Appelbaum
  - Item 10: The Wagner Act and the Question of Workplace Representation, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: David Brody
  - Item 11: Statement of Samuel Estreicher, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Samuel Estreicher
  - Item 12: Harris Poll Suggests Continuing Erosion of Labor Union Support and Influence Made Worse by Fight Against NAFTA, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Humphrey Taylor
    Notes: January 31, 1994.
  - Item 13: List of Dunlop Commission Members, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: IUD Sets Bold Agenda for Workplace Rights, Economic Empowerment and 'Democracy on the Job', 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: IUD Action
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1994:Jan./Feb.)
- Febuary 24, 1994 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Worker Participation in Management Decision Making, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Haruo Shimada
    Notes: February 6, 1994. A draft prepared for the Conference on International Evidence.
  - Item 2: News: Worker-Management Commission to Issue Fact Finding Report in May, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: February 10, 1994.
  - Item 3: Agenda for Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: February 24, 1994.
  - Item 4: Statement of William J. Kilberg, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: William J. Kilberg
  - Item 5: Statement of Clifford J. Ehrlich, Senio Vice President, Human Resources, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Clifford J. Ehrlich
  - Item 6: Statement of Clifford J. Ehrlich, Senio Vice President, Human Resources, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: February 24, 1994. Copy 2.
  - Item 7: Testimony of Allison Porter, Director of Recruitment and Training, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Allison Porter
  - Item 8: Statement of Bruce H. Simon, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Bruce H. Simon
  - Item 9: Statement of Matthew W. Finkin, Professor of Law and Professor of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Matthew W. Finkin
  - Item 10: Statement of Julius Getman, Professor of Law, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Julius Getman
  - Item 11: Statement of Henry S. Farber, Professor of Economics, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Henry S. Farber
  - Item 12: Testimony of John J. Lawler, Associate Professor of Labor, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: John J. Lawler
- March 16, 1994 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: International Evidence: Worker-Management Institutions and Economic Performance, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 14-15, 1994.
  - Item 2: Panel 4: Multinational Corporation in Worker-Management Relations and Economic Performance in Different National Settings, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Peter Stirling
  - Item 3: News: Dunlop Commission Meeting to Focus on the Foreign Experience with Worker-Management Relations, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 15, 1994.
  - Item 4: Agenda for Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 16, 1994.
  - Item 5: Promoting Systemic Change in Industrial Relations: Creating the Conditions of Effective Workplace Participation, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Wolfgang Streeck
  - Item 6: What Works (And Does Not Work) In Industrial Relations System Change to Promote Effective Workplace Participation? France, 1981 and Thereafter, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Jacques Rojot
  - Item 7: Co-Operative Labour-Management Relations in Australia, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Bruce Hartnett
  - Item 8: Worker Participation and Organisational Change in Australian Workplaces, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Margaret Gardner
- April 6, 1994 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agenda for Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 6, 1994.
  - Item 2: Statement of Charles G. Bakely, Jr., 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Charles G. Bakely, Jr.
  - Item 3: Statement of the American Civil Liberties Union, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Lewis L. Maltby
  - Item 4: Alternative Dispute Resolution as an Alternative to the Litigation of Non-Union Employee Claims of Illegal Termination, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Paul H. Tobias
  - Item 5: Testimony of 9 to 5, The National Association of Working Women, et al., 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Judith L. Lichtman; Sheila B. Coates; Heidi Hartmann; Francine Moccio
    Notes: April 6, 1994. Includes testimony of: 9 to 5, the National Association of Working Women; American Nurses Association; Black Women United for Action; Business and Profession Women/USA; Center for Advancement of Public Policy; Center for Policy Alternatives
  - Item 6: Statements of Interest of 9 to 5, The National Association of Working Women, et al., 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: What Do Unions Do For Women?, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Heidi Hartmann
  - Item 8: Statement of Clyde Summers, Professor of Law, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Clyde Summers
  - Item 9: Testimony of Katherine Van Wezel Stone, Professor of Law, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Katherin Van Wezel Stone
  - Item 10: Statement of Theodore J. St. Antoine, Professor of Law, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Theodore J. St. Antoine
  - Item 11: Minutes of Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Minutes of Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 6, 1994. Copy 2.
  - Item 13: Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations; Notice of Closing of Public Record, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 18, 1994.
- Dunlop Commission Fact Finding Report, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Fact Finding Report: Executive Summary, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: May, 1994.
- Dunlop Commission Fact Finding Report, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Fact Finding Report on the Future of Worker-Management Relations Released Today, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 2, 1994.
- August 10, 1994 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Dunlop Commission Fact Finding Report May, 1944 Analysis and Comment, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Ellis Boal
    Notes: August 4, 1994.
  - Item 2: Agenda for Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: August 10, 1994.
  - Item 3: The Nature and Extent of Employee Involvement in the American Workplace, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Aerospace Industries Association; Electronic Industries Association; Labor Policy Association; National Association of Manufacturers; Organization Resources Counselors
  - Item 4: Statement of Don Rainville on behalf of The National Association of Manufacturers, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Don Rainville
  - Item 5: Statement of the Labor Policy Association, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Steven M. Darien
  - Item 6: Statement of Rosemary M. Collyer on behalf of The National Association of Manufacturers, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Rosemary M. Collyer
  - Item 7: Statement of Chester McCammon on behalf of The National Association of Manufacturers, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Chester McCammon
  - Item 8: Statement of David M. Silberman, Director, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: David M. Silberman
  - Item 9: Statement of Richard Bensinger, Executive Director, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Richard Bensinger
  - Item 10: Statement of Richard Bensinger, Executive Director, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Statement of Arnold E. Perl appearing on behalf of "The Working Group", 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Arnold E. Perl
  - Item 12: Statement of Kenneth McLennan, President, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Kenneth McLennan
    Notes: August 3, 1994.
  - Item 13: Remarks of Jack West, Chairman, ASQC, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Jack West
  - Item 14: Testimony of ASQC, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Statement of James Perley, President, and Mary Burgan, General Secretary, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: James Perley; Mary Burgan
- September 8, 1994 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agenda for Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: September 8, 1994.
  - Item 2: Statement of Thomas R. Donahue, Secretary-Treasurer, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: Thomas R. Donahue
  - Item 3: Statement of John C. Read, Chairman, NAM Employee Relations Committee, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: John C. Read
  - Item 4: Statement of Howard V. Knicely, Executive Vice President, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Continuing Need to Distinguish Between Myth and Reality, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: Edward B. Miller
  - Item 6: Statement of Andrew M. Kramer appearing on behalf of "The Management Lawyers Working Group", 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: Andrew M. Kramer
  - Item 7: Statement of the American Civil Liberties Union, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Testimony of Herbert R. Northrup, Professor Emeritus of Management, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: Herbert R. Northrup
  - Item 9: Employee Participation or Labor Militancy, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- September 29, 1994 Meeting of the Dunlop Commission, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Alternative Dispute Resolution in the Workplace, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Joseph M. Stevens, Jr.
    Notes: September 28, 1994.
  - Item 2: Agenda for Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 29, 1994.
  - Item 3: Agenda for Meeting, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 29, 1994. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: Executive Summary of Testimony of Center for Advancement of Public Policy, et al., 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Martha Burk; Judith L. Lichtman; Nancy B. Kreiter
    Notes: September 29, 1994. Includes testimony of American Nurses Assocation; Black Women United for Action; Business and Profession Women/USA; Center for Advancement of Public Policy; Center for Women Policy Studies; Church Women United; Clearinghouse on Women's
  - Item 5: Testimony of Center for Advancement of Public Policy, et al., 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Oral Statement of Judith L. Lichtman, President, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Judith L. Lichtman
  - Item 7: Oral Statement of Nancy Kreiter, Research Director, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Nancy B. Kreiter
  - Item 8: Statement of the Labor Policy Association, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Joseph F. Vella
  - Item 9: Testimony of Lawrence Z. Lorber on behalf of the National Association of Manufacturers, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Lawrence Z. Lorber
  - Item 10: Statement on Alternative Forms of Dispute Resolution, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Thomas M. Duffy
  - Item 11: Statement of Samuel Estreicher, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Statement of Samuel Estreicher, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Testimony before the Dunlop Commission, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Arnold M. Zack
  - Item 14: Alternative Dispute Resolution and Agricultural Workers, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Nelson Carrasquillo
  - Item 15: Statement of William B. Gould IV, Professor of Law, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: William B. Gould IV
  - Item 16: Testimony of Frederick L. Feinstein, General Counsel, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Frederick L. Feinstein
- ILR Catherwood Library Hot Topic: "Future Worker" documents from January, 1995, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Using the Dunlop Report to Full Advantage: A Strategy for Achieving Mutual Gains, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Author: Thomas A. Kochan
    Notes: January 11, 1995.
  - Item 2: Dissenting Opinion of Douglas A. Fraser, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Author: Douglas A. Fraser
    Notes: January 3, 1995.